we all have aspirations and we work hard
to fulfill them this could be taking our
family on a yearly vacation of funding
child's education introducing I see I
see Andrew Luck sure income a unique
plan that gives you the flexibility to
receive your regular income to fulfill
your aspirations let us understand the
benefits of ICICI prolix income in
detail one income benefit choose to
receive regular income for a period of
five ten or fifteen years to get
guaranteed value benefits and bonus in
the form of regular additions to boost
your income free life cover to secure
your family's future during the policy
term let's understand this with an
example
Akshay invests in I see I see a true
luxury income and pays one lakh rupees
for 10 years from the 15th year he gets
an income of around 1.9 lakh rupees for
15 years which means he pays 10 lakh
rupees and can get up to 28 point 7 lakh
rupees
Akshay can choose to receive income for
5 10 or 15 years that's not all there
are more benefits
Akshay gets a life cover of 10 lakh
rupees for the entire policy term he can
receive dual tax savings on both
premiums paid and benefits received in
case of emergency liquidity needs he has
an option to take a loan against the
policy at a very attractive rate so what
are you waiting for
invest in icic Andrew Luck SIA income
today